One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Adventure on the Archipelago
of Dancing Soap Bubbles
It's good!
Right?
Hacchin's takoyaki is the best in the world, isn't it?
I can't stop, I'm unstoppable!
This takoyaki is great!
It really is good.
How does he bring out the taste of the sauce like this?
There's just something great about a food stall at sea, huh?
This is the first time I have ever eaten takoyaki.
It tastes really good.
It feels like my stomach is going to burst...
... although I have no stomach.
Eat as much as you like, it's free today!
It's our way of thanking you for saving us!
These have Dashi in them, and these have Mochi.
They're hot, so be careful.
So...
What does she think...?
Uh, Nami, I mean...
Uh...
Well...
H-How does it taste?
It's not like I'll forgive you just because of this, you know.
Of course not!
That's not what I meant!
I just wanted to know what you think, honestly!
It's really good!
Really?
Is that so?
Great, what a relief!
Alright, you guys!
Feel free to eat as much as you want!
Yeah! Just keep making more!
I'll eat all of it!
Hey, you guys~!
Young masters~!
Who's that?
That voice...
Wait, wait!
Don't leave without giving us a chance to thank you!
I'm Handsome...
Oh, that was wrong.
It's me, Duval!
Was that how his face looked...?
I altered his bone-structure.
He shouldn't have anything to complain about now, right?
My, Master Black Leg...
After you smashed my face in, we were all really surprised when I woke up!
You've made me really handsome!
I can't even recognize myself any more!
Now, the ladies will be crazy for me.
I must say...
It truly is a rosy life!
I want to go back to my lazy country-life as soon as possible...
But if I left without showing my thanks to you, I could never forgive myself!
This is your first time visiting these parts, right?
If there's anything we can help you with, just call us!
Don't wink if you're not used to it!
Well, as long as you're satisfied, that's good enough.
If you wanna do us a favor, then don't bother us again...
Beautiful...
Too beautiful!
Are you even listening?!
I want to ride on a white horse...
Hey, listen!
Head...
Head!
Listen to what he's saying!
Oh, that's right...
What?
I'm handsome?
I never said a single word about that!
It is somewhat embarrassing, but... I accept it!
Your fair maiden's kiss~!
I wasn't doing anything like that!
I was just wiping off the takoyaki!
What's with that ridiculously positive attitude of yours?!
Oh, mirror, mirror...
Am I the most handsome man in the world?
You're only giving it one choice?!
We get that you're handsome, but you're still an idiot.
Jealousy?
No way!
Stop it, Usopp!
You're no match against his craziness!
Well then, young master!
This is my snail phone number.
Feel free to call me whenever you like!
I'll definitely help you out when that time comes!
I really did cause you a lot of trouble, huh?
I am really... sorry!
Let's go, Rosy Life Riders!
Yes, handsome!
Hurry up and go.
Ah, I'm full!
Ah, I ate a lot!
I'm in Heaven!
Ah, what a wonderful afternoon...
This is the first time I have eaten takoyaki..
I am quite satisfied, too.
Ah, excuse me.
That was too dirty!
I'm exhausted...
They sure ate a lot...
As expected of the Straw Hat crew...
I wish I had six more arms.
Good job, Hachi!
Seems like they're all satisfied.
Really?
Then, I'm satisfied too.
That was really good!
I can't eat any more...
Hey!
Octopus, starfish, Camie-chan!
If you want a break, then come up to the deck.
I'll give you a cup of tea.
Yeah!
That's some good tea!
This is the course we're gonna take.
We're headed for the Sabaody Archipelago.
We can't get to Fishman Island without going there first?
We Fishmen and merfolk can just dive straight down to go back.
But you're humans, so if you tried to dive down there, the pressure would kill you!
Indeed...
The submarine couldn't reach it either.
Alright, pay attention!
It seems like you don't know anything...
So I'll tell you a thing or two about these seas!
Huh?
Who is gonna do that?
That...
Would...
Be...
Me!
Uh, would you please listen?
To start with, there are actually two routes you can take to reach the New World!
But only one of them is accessible for outlaws, like yourselves!
Why?
Well, that's because...
One requires the World Government's permission,
for you to cross the Red Line by going over the top,
through the Holy Land Mariejoa at its summit!
Of course, there's no way a pirate would be allowed to pass through like that.
You mean, walking over the Red Line?
Then what would we do about the ship?
You'd have to leave the ship behind, and get a new one on the other side.
Leave the ship behind?!
Yeah.
Getting permission takes both time and money, but it's the safest way to get there.
However...
Huh?
The passage you're taking will allow you to get through with your ship and everything!
That passage is known as...
The Ocean-floor Route, which goes straight by Fishman Island!
But the Ocean-floor Route is pretty dangerous as well.
Huh?
Camie, Camie?
What do you mean?
I didn't say you could take over...
There are plenty of people who are eaten, along with their ships, by sea-monsters and Sea Kings.
Hey!
I get it...
That would be pretty dangerous.
Right?
I don't want to go to Fishman Island after all...
Me neither...
Wait a minute, Camie!
Did you just say "along with their ships"?
Huh?
Yeah!
What kind of ship can we use to travel on the ocean-floor?
This ship.
Huh?
Hey, this ship can't travel under water!
No, it'll be alright.
Huh?
You see, inside of that huge wall, that circles the whole globe, the Red Line...
there's a small hole in a certain spot.
Although from our perspective, it's a huge hole.
And that's where Fishman Island is!
Actually, it's right underneath the Holy Land, Mariejoa!
You just head about ten thousand meters down, and there it is!
That far down?
It's a really nice place!
Wasn't Sky Island about ten thousand meters up in the sky, too?
What do you mean, we're going to take this ship to the ocean-floor?
We're going to get the ship coated at the island we're going to now.
Coated?
Now, look ahead!
Everyone, we're here!
It's beautiful!
What is that?
Something's flying around...
Well, I must say...
A true wonder.
Bubbles...?
This is...
Grand Line
Sabaody Archipelago
Sabaody Archipelago!
There's tons of soap-bubbles floating around!
Beautiful!
What's going on?
They just keep floating up, one after another...
Who's blowing them all?
They're rising up from the island.
Just saying that they're rising doesn't really help...
Why?
If I may...
Sorry for interrupting, but is the Log Pose alright?
Oh, right...
It's still pointing to Fishman Island, but...
Say, won't this island cause it to change its course?
You don't have to worry about that.
The Sabaody Archipelago is just a lot of trees.
Then, those aren't really islands?
Correct.
Have you ever heard of mangrove trees?
You mean trees with roots in the ocean that sink and emerge with the tides, right?
That's right.
Although the mangroves here never sink.
The Sabaody Archipelago is the largest mangrove in the world.
They call the trees here the Yarukiman Mangroves.
"Yaru ki manman": To be pumped up.
Pumped up groves?
Yeah, they sure look like they're excited!
I'm getting excited too!
In all, there are 79 trees, and all of them are like small islands.
There are towns or other structures on each one.
All of the islands together are known as the Sabaody Archipelago.
The closest grove, grove 44, is the civilian entrance, so let's take the ship a little closer.
Now that we're seeing them up-close, those roots really are huge, huh?
Is that a bridge?
Yeah.
That's how each of the islands are connected.
Alright, we're here!
This is grove 41.
This is where we're dropping anchor.
I'm setting foot on it first!
Alright everyone, don't forget the number here!
Like I said earlier...
All of the islands are connected via bridges...
So if you remember the number, you won't get lost.
Even then, there is one guy who'll get lost, right?
There is.
Huh, what?
What is it?!
One popped out from the ground!
That's really funny!
Awesome!
I got on it!
It's not popping, huh?
That's really nice!
Those soap-bubbles really are mysterious.
How do they work?
The roots of these Yarukiman Mangroves... secrete a unique kind of resin.
Oh, no!
This is all sticky.
Don't wipe it off!
So, when the trees "breathe out", the resin is blown out as well, and forms these soap-bubbles.
I see...
So that's why they're all floating into the sky?
So all of this is actually natural?
Hey!
Huh?
Hey, Luffy!
When did you get up there?!
I can see an amusement park over there!
Let's go!
Let's ride the ferris wheel!
An amusement park?
That's the Sabaody Park.
How nice...
The ferris wheel...
Riding on that is my dream.
Your dream?
Why can't you ride it?
Don't be ridiculous!
You can't do that, Camie!
Yeah, I know...
I want to ride it too, but I guess I can't...
By the way, Hachi...
What's our goal on this island?
You said something about coating for the ship earlier, didn't you?
We have to find a coating mechanic, and have him coat your ship with this resin!
Simply put, that will enable your ship to travel under the sea!
Seriously?
That's the only way humans can reach Fishman Island.
However, if you get an amateur to do it...
The ship, and the humans riding it, would be crushed by the water-pressure.
I know one mechanic who's trustworthy, so I'm gonna take you to him.
Octopus-san, you are such a nice fellow for helping us so much...
Ah, he is a nice octopus!
In exchange...
I'd like you to make just a single promise to me.
Sure, what is it?
Once we enter the city, we might run into the World Nobles walking around there.
Who are they?
The citizens of the Holy Land, Mariejoa.
And, what about them?
No matter what might happen in the city...
I want you to promise that you won't lay a hand on the World Nobles!
Even if someone were to be killed...
Right before your very eyes...
Just pretend you didn't see anything!
Everyone left for the town...
You're not going?
We used up all our cola in that battle back there.
Taking care of the ship is my job!
Of course, I wanted to help out as well!
Once we're done, let's head out, all three of us.
This island looks fun!
Nah...
I can't leave the ship before someone comes back.
Huh, why?
Well, you see...
My beloved Nami-san said...
Hmm, this is a problem...
We've got tons of treasure stored on the ship right now...
Is there a knight around who would safeguard it?
Ta-daah!
It's me!
You really do anything Nami wants you to, huh?
I am a slave of love!
There's no point if you admit it yourself...
Huh?
Hey!
Zoro!
Hello?!
Zoro-kun?!
Where are you going, all by yourself?
For a walk.
So what?
Stop it!
Don't! You'll get lost, dammit!
This is an Archipelago, you know?!
We won't be able to find you!
Like I'd get lost!
Who'd get lost on an island like this, where it's so easy to find your way?
Each of the trees have a number on them, right?
Even a kid with the worst sense of direction would be able to find his way!
You'd thought that far ahead?
I didn't think of that.
Sorry!
Be careful!
Don't forget to ask for directions!
Don't believe in yourself!
They're going way overboard.
As long as I don't forget the number on this tree...
Number one, right?
The World Nobles are also known as the Celestial Dragons.
They're really arrogant, and wear a mask so they don't have to breathe the same air as everyone else.
No matter what, don't try to oppose those guys.
I need you to promise that!
Sure!
And there are several other things to look out for.
Like I said earlier, this island is where everyone who wants to go to the New World, gathers.
There are plenty of big-name pirates like yourselves...
And then there are marines and bounty-hunters trying to catch them.
Also...
Kidnappers!
Even if pirates are taken away by slave-traders, the law won't protect them.
If you do anything to get yourselves noticed, they'll go after you instantly, so be careful!
The marines around here are not to be taken lightly.
These waters are close to the Navy HQ, after all.
All the bounty-hunters around here are on a totally different level as well!
And there's one more thing...
What's that?
You're too concerned about stuff!
Camie and I are not a mermaid and a fishman, okay?
While we're here, please pretend that we're ordinary people.
Why?
It's just easier that way.
We should follow the customs of the culture around here, Luffy.
Let's just do as the octopus told us to.
There we go...
Slowly, slowly...
I'm in!
How amusing!
It really is mysterious...
I'm getting into it!
None of the air is coming out, either!
Well, then...
How about putting this in?
Like this?
Is that about the right height?
Now you can drive around with it.
I'm moving!
Awesome!
This is fun!
It is not breaking!
Aren't they convenient, the Sabaody Archipelago's exclusive Bubble Bike?
How about it?
If you want to rent it, it's 500 Belly per person.
If you want to buy it, it's 1,000 Belly!
Cheap, isn't it?
Then, we'll rent one.
I want one!
I'm gonna buy it with my spending money!
Me too, me too!
Don't.
There's no point in buying it, just rent one.
Why should you get to decide that?
That's right!
Uh, I'll tell you the reason later.
Old man!
We'll rent two more of them.
Oh, you're a local, huh? That's too bad...
This feels great!
I'm definitely buying one of these Bubble bikes!
Straw Hat...
You rode the soap bubbles into the sky when we first got here, right?
Why did you fall?
Oh, well, when I reached the top of the trees, I thought I'd go even higher...
But then all the soap bubbles around me suddenly started popping...
And then the one I was riding did, too...
So, I ended up falling.
That's because you left the Sabaody Archipelago's unique atmosphere.
This place has a special, unique climate specifically suited to the Yarukiman Mangroves.
But once you leave that climate, the soap bubbles won't be strong enough to stay whole.
Is that so?
Then, that means that you can only ride the soap bubbles...
for as long as you stay on the island, doesn't it?
That's how it is.
People who come here for the first time often buy a Bubble bike...
But that's basically a rip-off.
Renting one is good enough.
No, I think I'll buy one!
I don't accept that explanation at all...
You don't get it, do you?
In short, once you leave the island, the soap bubbles will break.
It's mysterious, isn't it?
What?!
They just mysteriously break?
Why didn't you say so right away?!
Ah, but Luffy-chin, you can use them at Fishman Island.
We've got soap bubbles on the ocean floor too.
I wanna go to Fishman Island soon~
I'm really looking forward to it~
In that case, you should meet the mermaid princess!
She's so beautiful, I can't even describe it!
I can't look away from her myself!
I will be looking forward to that!
I have a good eye for beauties...
Though being a skeleton, I do not have eyes.
Eh, are you listening?
Wow, this looks good!
What's Graman?
They're Grand Line Manjuus!
Manjuu: Steamed bun
Or Graman for short.
Would you like to taste some?
You can see that it's got "Grand Line First Half" written on it, right?
The idea is to take them into the New World as a souvenir of sorts.
They'll last for about three months, so don't worry about it!
This tastes great!
May I open another package?
Aren't you gonna buy any?!
Grove 35...
There are lots of hotels here, aren't there?
It's the living quarters for those waiting for permission to pass through Mariejoa.
It's really easy to make these hotels...
See that over there?
They just coat those huge soap bubbles in a special alloy, and the foundation is done.
That's how they make those round buildings.
Really?
Robin!
Isn't that a shopping mall?!
Come back any time!
Grasen...
Grachoco...
A key-holder!
A pennant!
Hold on to those memories!
You bought a lot of them, huh?
Carrying that around everywhere should be a problem...
Put them in the Bubble bag.
Bubble bag?
It's so light!
You don't need to put in any effort to carry your luggage on this island, huh?
Huh?
Where did Nami and Robin go?
They went to the shopping mall in Grove 30.
They said they'd leave the coating of the ship to us.
Oh, so that's it?
Right!
Leave it to us!
Even though we invited her, Camie-chan wouldn't come with us...
She's seemed more reserved ever since we arrived on this island...
What could be bothering Camie?
Perhaps there is some sort of bad history on this island...?
Bad history...?
I'm in the lead!
Don't get cocky!
There's still a long way to go!
Go, Hacchin!
How did this turn into a race?
What's all the commotion about?
I'm begging you!
Hey!
I'm asking you a favor here!
Anyone's fine!
An axe!
A saw!
Anything will do!
Just give me something!
I just want to get this off my neck!
I won't hurt anyone!
Please let go of me...
I don't want to die...
I've given up on going to the New World!
I've got a wife and a child back home!
I'm begging you!
Please lend me a hand!
I wanna go home!
Last time I saw my kid, he was still a baby...
He still doesn't even know what I look like!
I'm begging you!
He's...
I wanna go home!
Hey, please!
Please help me!
Don't get involved.
He's probably a pirate who was caught by kidnappers and sold as a slave...
His owner probably brought him to this island, and he made a run for it!
Even though he should know that he can't escape!
W-What's that sound?
Damn!
This ring!
If I could just get this off my neck!
Damn it!
No!
Stop!
Please stop!
Hey!
Damn it all to Hell!
Slaves always have those chains attached to their necks...
If they try to take them off or run away, they'll explode!
Just let me buy some souvenirs and go home...
I've given up on being a pirate...
It's a slave who tried to run away!
Get away!
Don't get involved with him!
L-Look at that...
We have to help him!
Idiot!
You promised to not get involved, no matter what, right?!
What's with this city?!
Hacchin, what are we going to do?!
The Celestial Dragons are nearby!
It's alright.
Calm down, Camie!
Straw Hat!
Get out of the Bubble bike!
Huh?
Why?
Just hurry up and do it!
Uh, sure...
They're here!
Are those the Celestial Dragons?
You have to bow down too!
Why?
No matter what, don't look them in the eyes!
My, how vulgar, Saruu!
Them, huh?
Celestial Dragon
Saint Roswald Celestial Dragon
Saint Shalria
Oh no, Father.
Yet another one has been broken.
Did you make sure to give him his tranquilizer every day?
Why, yes, I did.
However, it appears that it does not work on fools...
Would you please buy me a new one?
Your disciplining skills are truly terrible.
You keep destroying my captain collection, one after another...
This one is certainly useless.
A grown man always crying about family this, family that...
You are just a mere human!
He can't even move any more!
You disgust me!
Why, that-!
Please, wait!
I would like a giant slave next.
You should start with a human child.
But I detest the weak.
Please don't do anything rash!
It's the marines!
Move it, move it!
First off, we should get away from here!
How about some tea?
It will help you calm down.
I feel terrible...
Do you think that guy will be alright?
He's a pirate, so even if they save him, he'll just be sent to prison.
That pirate should be able to beat that old guy and the woman, right?
Why?!
If you hurt one of the Celestial Dragons...
An admiral from Navy HQ and a fleet of battle ships will come here.
An admiral...
Aokiji?!
It could be Akainu or Kizaru...
There's no way to know who'd show up.
The HQ is right next to us, after all.
What makes those guys so special?!
Those guys are descendants of the creators!
The creators?
800 years ago, a group of 20 kings formed the organization known as the World Government.
The Celestial Dragons are their descendants.
And over the course of the years...
They've come to abuse their incredible influence.
The Celestial Dragons...